Finding Aid for the Louis Jolyon West Papers LSC.0590
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Restricted Materials
  - Scientology--Litigation--Wollersheim v. Church of Scientology of California (3 of 3) (separated)., 1990. (Box 265, Folder 4)
    Contains material marked "confidential."
  - Scientology--Litigation--Wright case., 1992-1993. (Box 265, Folder 5)
    Contains personal information about Scientology member.
  - Scientology--Research--Miscellaneous (3 of 3) (separated)., 1950, 1991-1992. (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Scientology--Stanford Research Institute (separated)., 1992. (Box 265, Folder 7)
    Contains information marked confidential.
  - Shepherding (separated)., 1981. (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - Stop Abuse by Counselors (separated)., 1991, 1993. (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - Sullivanians/Sullivanism movement (separated)., 1987. (Box 265, Folder 10)
    Contains material marked confidential.
  - Temple of Set (separated)., 1976, ca. 1984. (Box 265, Folder 11)
  - Transcendental Meditation (TM) (separated)., 1987, 1991. (Box 265, Folder 12)
    Contains patient/referral information.
  - Unification Church--The Collegiate Association for the Research of Principles (C.A.R.P.) (separated)., 1983. (Box 265, Folder 13)
    Contains personal employment information.
  - Unification Church--"Ticket to Heaven" movie (separated)., 1981. (Box 265, Folder 14)
    Contains personal information regarding members' families.
  - Unification Church--Correspondence., 1976. (Box 265, Folder 15)
  - University Bible Fellowship (separated)., 1981, 1990, 1996-1997. (Box 265, Folder 16)
  - Wellspring/Paul Martin (separated)., 1989, 1991. (Box 265, Folder 17)
    Contains LJW patient information.
  - Wingspread Conference: "Cultism: A Conference for Scholars and Policy Makers"--Support for conference correspondence (separated)., 1981. (Box 265, Folder 18)
  - Yogic meditation., 1988. (Box 265, Folder 19)
    Contains personal and psychiatric referral information.
  - CIA/Mind control., 1978. (Box 265, Folder 20)
    Contains personal medical information.
  - News clippings--confidential letters., 1977. (Box 265, Folder 21)
  - LJW patient notes., undated. (Box 265, Folder 22)
    Contains patient information.
  - LJW typewritten account "Some Notes on Being Assaulted by Threat"., 1963. (Box 265, Folder 23)
  - "Color of Tears" (separated)., 1962. (Box 265, Folder 24)
    Interview marked "Confidential"; contains psychiatric information.
  - Edmondson v. Hill's Van Service (separated)., 1997. (Box 265, Folder 25)
    Contains correspondence between attorneys and LJW regarding details of case.
  - Letters of inquiry (separated)., 1973. (Box 265, Folder 26)
    Contains letter from prospective patient asking for treatment.
  - Alcoholism--"Therapeutic Interventions in Alcoholism" (separated)., 1979. (Box 265, Folder 27)
    Contains letter and draft of paper identified as confidential.